jobgroupz.com 2011-06-02

# JobGroupz.com - Real Time Job Seach Made Easy

Website Privacy Policy 

By using this JobGroupz.com Website, you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

Changes to the Privacy Policy   
We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Any changes will be posted on this page and visitors are encouraged to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Website following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

Information Collection and Use  
We collect information on the Site at two different stages. First, we collect  
anonymous, aggregate information (such as domain name or IP address) from all  
visitors to the Site. This type of information is never linked to any personally  
identifiable information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical  
reports about the use of the Site. Second, we may require the submission of certain personally identifiable information when you use the features of or services available on this Site.

Cookies and Privacy    
Although some cookies provide a useful function, many others may not be desirable. As the Internet has evolved from its beginnings in academia and government to a commercial enterprise, cookies have inevitably been turned into a tracking mechanism used by advertisers. In principle, cookies are only accessible to the site that originated them but large advertising agencies with many clients can easily circumvent this restriction by collecting information for all their clients under one domain. A fairly harmless (and perhaps even useful) advertising application of cookies is to rotate banner ads as you go from page to page to make sure that you do not see the same ads over and over. However, there are more invasive tracking methods that might involve cookies and therein arise privacy issues 

**  What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**   
The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

**Contact Information**

For further information about this site, products or services, please contact our support team.
